Register of the Guy Jean Pauker Papers, 1928-1996
Hoover Institution Archives
- INDONESIA SUBJECT FILE, 1945-1980. (Box 6-62)
  - Education
    - Bruner, Edward M. and Elaine C., Anthropological Perspectives on Primary Education in Indonesia, August 1969 (Folder 7)
    - Education Objectives Workshop, Djakarta, September 13-24, 1971 (Folder 8)
    - Engineering education, 1955-1965 (Folder 9)
    - Heckelman, T. Jack and Kartomo Wirosuhardjo, The Systems Approach to Educational Reform in Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 10)
    - Indonesian students going to the United States, orientation course, 1957 (Folder 11)
    - Kentucky at Bandung, March 1968, University of Kentucky in affiliation with Institut Teknologi Bandung (Technological University at Bandung) (Folder 12)
    - Kentucky at Bogor, March 1968, University of Kentucky in affiliation with the Institut Pertanian Bogor (Agricultural University at Bogor) (Folder 13)
    - Office of Educational Development
      - National Assessment of Education, December 1971 (Box 22., Folder 1)
      - Permanency of Literacy, June 1971 (Folder 2)
      - Primary Task Force
        - Study of Headmasters, June 1971 (Folder 3)
        - Survey of Teacher Characteristics, July 1971 (Folder 4)
      - Reports on visits of the Assessment Survey Team, March 1971 (Folder 5)
      - UNESCO and AIR contract, 1971 (Folder 6)
    - Primary school curriculum development, 1970 (Folder 7)
    - Primary Task Force
      - Experts' observation of classroom (Folder 8)
      - Primary schools, 1971 (Folder 9)
      - Relationships between elements in the system, 1971 (Folder 10)
      - Survey of Madrassahs, 1971 (Folder 11)
      - Survey of primary schools, n.d. (Folder 12)
      - Teacher Project, 1970 (Folder 13)
    - Slors, Peter A.
      - Some Bottlenecks in Indonesia's Educational Structure, With a View on it's Future, January 12, 1971 (Folder 14)
      - The Use of Rough Statistical Data on Primary Education For Pre-Planning Purposes, May 22, 1971 (Folder 15)
    - Statistics
      - 1955-56 (Box 23., Folder 1)
      - 1956-57 (Folder 2)
      - 1970-71 (Folder 3)
      - 1970-72 (Folder 4)
    - Thomas, R. Murray, Economics and Education in Indonesia, 1940-1966, n.d. (Folder 5)
    - UNESCO
      - Educational Research, Planning and Development Project, 1970-71 (Folder 6)
      - Sponsored report on the organization of B.P.P., April 1972 (Folder 7)
    - Universities, 1958-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Embassy, Washington, D.C.
    - General (Folder 9-10)
    - Information Division
      - Focus On Indonesia
        - 1967-68 (Folder 11)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 24., Folder 1)
        - 1974-77 (Folder 2)
        - 1977-1980 (Folder 3)
      - A Survey on the Controversial Problem of the Establishment of the Federation of Malaysia, March 1964 (Folder 4)
    - Information Section, Indonesian News and Views
      - 1964 (Folder 5)
      - 1967-68 (Folder 6)
      - 1969 (Folder 7)
      - 1970-71 (Folder 8)
      - 1971-72 (Folder 9)
      - 1973 (Folder 10)
      - 1974 (Box 25., Folder 1)
      - 1975 (Folder 2)
    - Report on Indonesia, 1956, 1961-64 (Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation grants, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Foreign policy and defence (Folder 5)
  - Foreign relations
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Bunnell, Frederick P., Indonesia's Foreign Policy in the 1960s: President Sukarno Moves From Non-Alignment to Confirmation, May 1965 (Folder 7)
    - China
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Mozingo, David P., Sino-Indonesian Relations, 1955-1965, July 1965 (Folder 9)
    - Federspiel, Howard M., Indonesia and It's International Relations, July 1962 (Folder 10)
    - Japan (Folder 11)
    - Malaysia (Folder 12)
    - Modelski, George, Indonesia and Her Neighbors: Policy Alternatives for the West, memorandum, October 29, 1964 (Folder 13)
    - Netherlands, The (Folder 14)
    - Philippine Islands (Folder 15)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (Folder 16)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (Box 26., Folder 1)
    - United States of America (Folder 2)
    - Weinstein, Franklin B., The Uses of Foreign Policy in Indonesia, article, World Politics, Vol. 24, No. 3, April 1972 (Folder 3)
  - Forest Industries Development, National Pulp and Paper Survey, Canadian International Development Agency, March 15, 1972 (Folder 4)
  - Fourth Asian Games Bulletin, Djakarta, No. 2, 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Gailbraith, Francis J., Preliminary Observations For a Study of Javanese Culture, 1949 (Folder 6)
  - GANEFO, November 1963 (Folder 7-8)
  - General elections, report on, 1963 (Folder 9)
  - Gerakan Hidup Baru (New Life Movement), July-August 1957 (Folder 10)
  - Government replies to the general debates
    - First readings concerning the government's statements on
      - Sumatra affairs of December 1956, February 1957 (Box 27., Folder 1)
      - Cabinet Programme, made by Prime Minister Hadji Djuanda in the Plenary Meeting of the House of Representatives, May 1957 (Folder 2)
    - Second readings concerning the government's statements on
      - Sumatra affairs of December 1956, February 1957 (Folder 3)
      - Cabinet Programme, made by Prime Minister Hadji Djuanda in the Plenary Meeting of the House of Representatives, June 1957 (Folder 4)
  - Government statements on
    - Cabinet Programme, made by Prime Minister Hadji Djuanda before the Plenary Meeting of the House of Representatives, May 17, 1957 (Folder 5)
    - December events in Sumatra, made by Prime Minister Ali Sastroamidjojo in the Plenary Meeting of the House of Representatives, January 21, 1957 (Folder 6)
  - Hanna, Willard A., A Note on Indonesia, June 27, 1957 (Folder 7)
  - Harrison, Brian, Problems of Political Integration in Southeast, October 1955 (Folder 8)
  - Hawkins, Everett D., Labor Relations in a Newly Independent Country: The Case of Indonesia, January 12, 1957 (Folder 9)
  - History
    - General (Folder 10)
    - 20th century (Folder 11)
    - 1949-1951 (Folder 11A)
    - 1950-1966 (Folder 12-15)
    - 1951-52 (Box 28., Folder 1)
    - 1952 (Folder 2)
    - 1953 (Folder 4-7)
    - 1953-54 (Folder 8)
    - 1953-54 (Box 29., Folder 1)
    - 1954 (Folder 2-3)
    - 1954-55 (Folder 4)
    - 1955 (Folder 5-6)
    - 1955 (Box 30., Folder 1-2)
    - 1955-57 (Folder 3)
    - 1956 (Folder 4-7)
    - 1956-57 (Box 31., Folder 1)
    - 1957 (Folder 2-6)
    - 1958
      - January-March (Box 32., Folder 1-2)
      - April-December (Folder 3-4)
    - 1959 (Folder 5)
    - 1959 (Box 33., Folder 1)
    - 1960 (Folder 2)
    - 1960-61 (Folder 3-4)
    - 1962 (Folder 5-6)
    - 1963 (Folder 7)
    - 1964
      - January-March (Box 34., Folder 1-2)
      - April-December (Folder 3-4)
    - 1965
      - January (Folder 5)
      - February (Folder 6)
      - March (Folder 7)
      - April-May (Box 35., Folder 1)
      - July-August (Folder 2-3)
      - September (Folder 4)
      - October (Folder 5-7)
      - November (Box 36., Folder 1-2)
      - December (Folder 3)
    - 1966
      - January-February (Folder 4-5)
      - March (Folder 6-7)
      - April (Box 37., Folder 1-2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Box 38., Folder 1)
      - November (Folder 2)
      - December (Folder 3)
    - 1967
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Folder 7)
      - May-June (Box 39., Folder 1)
      - August-October (Folder 2)
      - November-December (Folder 3)
    - 1968
      - January-April (Folder 4)
      - May-August (Folder 5)
      - September-December (Folder 6)
    - 1969
      - January-June (Folder 7)
      - July-December (Box 40., Folder 1)
    - 1970 (Folder 2)
    - 1972-73 (Folder 3)
    - 1974 (Folder 4)
    - Coup d'etat, 1965 (Folder 5)
  - Immigration laws (Folder 6)
  - Indonesian Peasant Force (Barisan Tani Indonesia) (Box 41., Folder 1)
  - Indonesian university students - CGMI (Concentrated Movement of Indonesian University Students) (Folder 2)
  - Industry
    - Entrepreneurship in the Batik Industry of Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 3)
    - The Government's Program on Industries, report, University of Indonesia, Institute for Economic and Social Research, November 1954 (Folder 4)
    - The Industrial Urgency Plan, October 15, 1953 (Folder 5)
    - Rao, K. Nagaraja, Small Scale Industry and Economic Development in Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 6)
  - Irian Barat (Folder 7)
  - Japanese military administration in (Folder 8)
  - Japanese occupation of, 1942-45 (Folder 9)
  - Java
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Central Java, 1957 (Folder 11)
    - East Java
      - General (Folder 11A)
      - Armed forces, 1957 (Folder 12)
    - Geertz, Clifford, Ethnic vs. National Loyalties in the Indonesian Village: The Javanese Village, February 1959 (Folder 13)
    - Geertz, Hildred, The Vocabulary of Emotion - A Study of Javanese Socialization Processes, August 1959 (Folder 14)
    - Java Bank, 1952-53 (Folder 15)
    - Jay, Robert R., Religion and Politics in a Rural Javanese Community, n.d. (Folder 16)
    - Politics and government (Folder 17)
    - West Java
      - General (Folder 18)
      - Armed forces, 1962 (Box 42., Folder 1)
      - Arrested VIP and security, 1956-57 (Folder 2)
      - History, 1956-57 (Folder 3)
      - Sindanglaya Village, 1973 (Folder 4)
      - SOB regulations (Folder 5)
  - Johns, A. H.
    - Amir Hamzah: Malay Prince, Indonesian Poet, 1963 (Folder 6)
    - Devaruci or the Divine Splendour: A Javanese Presentation of an Indian Religious Concept, n.d. (Folder 7)
    - The Enlightenment of Bhima, n.d. (Folder 8)
    - Indonesian Democracy in Extremis, 1963 (Folder 9)
  - Judicial and legal systems
    - Lev, Daniel S.
      - The Development of the Islamic Judiciary in Indonesia: A Study in Institutional Change and Adaptation, n.d. (Folder 10)
      - Judicial System and Legal Culture in Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 11)
      - The Lady and the Banyan Tree: Civil Law Change in Indonesia, reprint, American Journal of Comparitive Law, Vol. 14, No. 2, Spring 1965 (Folder 12)
      - The Politics of Judicial Development in Indonesia, reprint, Comparative Studies in Society and History, Vol. VII, No. 2, January 1965 (Folder 13)
      - The Private Legal Professions, n.d. (Box 43., Folder 1)
  - Kahar Muzakar (Folder 2)
  - Kalimantan (Folder 3)
  - Kementerian Penerangan
    - 1956
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - 1957
      - January (Folder 7)
      - February (Folder 8)
      - March (Folder 9)
      - April (Folder 10)
      - May (Box 44., Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July (Folder 3)
      - August (Folder 4)
      - September (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
  - Kongres Rakjat (People's Congress), 1955-57 (Folder 7)
  - KRJT rebel gang and other rebellions, 1956-57 (Folder 8)
  - Language and literature
    - Alisjahbana, S. Takdir
      - The Development of the Indonesian Language and Literature, 1955 (Folder 9)
      - The Failure of Modern Linguistics in the Face of Linguistic Problems of the Twentieth Century, 1965 (Folder 10)
      - Indonesian Language and Literature: Two Essays, 1962 (Folder 11)
    - Anwar, Chairil, Sharp Gravel, 1960 (Folder 12)
  - Left-wing political movements, 1960 (Box 45., Folder 1)
  - Leifer, Michael, Indonesia's Future Role, article, The World Today, December 1970 (Folder 2)
  - Liddle, R. William, Evolution From Above: National Leadership and Local Development in Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 3)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. and Alan C. Rankin, Training For Administration in Indonesia, 1954 (Folder 4)
  - Mackie, J., Indonesia: A Background to `Confrontation', n.d. (Folder 5)
  - Maluku and Irian Barat (Folder 6)
  - Maps (Folder 7)
  - Mihardja, Achdiat K., Some Humorous and Satirical Aspects of Indonesian Stories, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Military and political officials, 1967-68 (Folder 9)
  - Miller, Ann R., The View From Djakarta, article, The New Leader, May 15, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - Ministry of Education
    - Draft Report of Systems Analysis Mission, June - October 1970 (Folder 11)
    - Programme of Educational Assistance to the Five Year Plan, Draft Report by the Minister of Education, July 1969
      - Installment 1 (Box 46., Folder 1)
      - Installment 2 (Folder 2)
  - Ministry of Education and Culture, Indonesia Education Project, 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Ministry of Information
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Draw Up a Constitution Which Is Really Needed Based On Res Publica, speech by the President of Indonesia, Constituent Assembly, November 10, 1956 (Folder 5)
    - For the Election of Members of the Constituent Assembly and of the House of Representatives, 1953 (Folder 6)
    - Indonesia Repudiates Debts to the Netherlands, August 10, 1956 (Folder 7)
    - Indonesia Through Foreign Eyes, 1956-57 (Folder 8)
    - Information Bulletin, Vol IV, No. 47, April 1968 (Folder 9)
    - Pantjasila (Folder 10)
    - Tito in Yugoslavia, December 1958 - January 1959 (Folder 11)
  - Mozingo, David, An Indonesian General's Views on Malaysia, December 11, 1963 (Folder 12)
  - Musjawarah Nasional (Folder 13)
  - Mysbergh, James H., The Indonesian Elite, article, Far Eastern Survey, March 1957 (Folder 14)
  - National Conference, September 10-15, 1957
    - General (Folder 15)
    - Local authorities (Folder 16)
    - Parliament and Dewan Nasional (Folder 17)
    - Political parties (Folder 18)
    - Press coverage (Folder 19)
  - National Defence Institute, Defence and Security Department, The Growth of the Indonesian Ocean Societies in the Next Decades, paper submitted to the Indian Ocean Conference, March 18-19, 1971 (Box 47., Folder 1)
  - National Defence and Security Council, Institute For Strategic Studies, Southeast Asia After the Vietnam War: Some Tentative Indonesian Views, December 20, 1972 (Folder 2)
  - National Institute of Administration, General Report on Local Government in Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 3)
  - National Seminar of Women Peasants, January 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Nationalism (Folder 5)
  - Natural resources (Folder 6)
  - Notowidigdo, Moekarto
    - Speech, American Indonesian Chamber of Commerce, New York City, October 11, 1956 (Folder 7)
    - Toward Economic Stability in Indonesia, speech, Far East America Council of Commerce and Industry October 4, 1956 (Folder 8)
  - Nugroho, address before the Council of World Affairs, San Francisco, January 9, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Nusa Tenggara (Folder 10)
  - Ohio University Center for International Studies, Southeast Asia Program, 1968, Public Protest in Indonesia, by Ann R. Willner (Folder 11)
  - Pauker, Ewa T., GANEFO I: Sports and Politics in Djakarta, March 31, 1964 (Folder 12)
  - Pelzer, Karl J., Geographical Literature on Indonesia, n.d. (Folder 13)
  - Pemuda Demokrat Indonesia (Indonesian Democratic Youth) (Folder 14)
  - Permanent Mission of the Republic of Indonesia to the United Nations
    - Information on Indonesia, 1959-1960 (Folder 15)
    - News and Views
      - 1963 (Folder 16)
      - 1964 (Folder 17-18)
    - Statement of Dr. Subandrio to the United Nations General Assembly on Monday, October 9, 1961 (Box 48., Folder 1)
  - Political parties
    - General (Folder 2-3)
    - 1953 (Folder 4-5)
    - 1954 (Folder 6-7)
    - 1955 (Folder 8)
    - 1955 (Box 49., Folder 1)
    - 1956 (Folder 2-3)
    - 1957 (Folder 4-6)
    - Grand Indonesia Party (Folder 7)
    - Partai Nasional Indonesia (Indonesia National Party) (Box 50., Folder 1)
    - Partai Sosialis Indonesia (Indonesian Socialist Party) (Folder 2)
  - Political preferences of Indonesians, 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Political prisoners (Folder 4)
  - Politics and government
    - 20th century (Folder 5)
    - 1950-1966
      - General (Folder 6-9)
      - General (Box 51., Folder 1-2)
      - Clippings (Folder 3-5)
    - 1966-1970 (Folder 6-7)
    - 1966-1970 (Box 52., Folder 1)
    - Cabinet, reorganized, March 6, 1962 (Folder 2)
    - Central government, clippings
      - 1953 (Folder 3)
      - 1954
        - January-July (Folder 4)
        - August-December (Folder 5)
      - 1955
        - January-August (Folder 6)
        - September-October (Folder 7)
        - November (Box 53., Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1956
        - January-March (Folder 3)
        - April-August (Folder 4)
        - September-November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1957 (Folder 7)
      - 1957
        - January-March (Box 54., Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May-June (Folder 3)
        - July-August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
    - Election laws, 1953-55 (Folder 6)
    - Territorial division of Indonesia (Folder 7)
    - Ulinski, John A., Some Aspects of Local Government in Indonesia, September 1954 (Folder 8)
    - Walker, Millidge, Decentralization in Guided Democracy: The Future of Local Government in Indonesia, March 1960 (Box 55., Folder 1)
  - Press
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Glossary of abbreviations and terms (Folder 3)
    - Harian Rakjat
      - Role of in Indonesian society, 1961 (Folder 4)
      - Selected articles from, 1960 (Folder 5)
      - Translations from, 1960 (Folder 6)
    - Kehidupan Partai (Party Life)
      - Selected articles from, 1960 (Folder 6A)
      - Selected translations, April-May 1959 (Folder 7)
    - KNI News Service (Folder 8)
    - Lists of newspapers and serials (Folder 9)
    - Lubis, Mochtar, The Press in Indonesia, June 1952 (Folder 10)
    - Selected articles from Indonesian newspapers (Folder 11)
    - Smith, Edward Cecil, A History of Newspaper Suppression in Indonesia, 1949-1965, August 1969 (Folder 12-13)
  - Proclamation of independence anniversaries (Folder 14-15)
  - The Provisional Constitution of the Republic of Indonesia and the Elucidation to Act No. 7, 1950 (Folder 16)
  - Psychology and psychotherapy (Box 56., Folder 1)
  - Religion (Folder 2)
  - Revolutionary Government of Indonesia; charters communiques, program, February 1958 (Folder 3)
  - Rice supply, 1957-58 (Folder 4)
  - RMS Movement, 1953-56 (Folder 5)
  - Santos, Gil, Indonesia Today, n.d. (Folder 6)
  - Sanusi, Anwar, speech, Djakarta, September 28, 1965 (Folder 7)
  - Sastroamidjojo, Ali, speech, World Affairs Council, Philadelphia, November 27, 1951 (Folder 8)
  - Schmitt, Hans O., Summary of Indonesian Developments, December 1957 (Folder 9)
  - Science and technology (Folder 10)
  - Security (Folder 11)
  - Social conditions
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Investigation About Standard and Plane of Living in Indonesia, Institute of Economic and Social Research and the Indonesian Institute of World Affairs, Djakarta, 1954 (Folder 13)
    - The Urbanization of Djakarta, edited by H. J. Heeren, n.d., University of Indonesia, Institute of Economic and Social Research Project (Folder 14)
    - Wertheim, W. F., Sociological Aspects of Inter-Island Migration in Indonesia, reprint, Population Studies, Vol. XII, No. 3, March 1959 (Folder 15)
  - Social structure (Folder 16)
  - Soedjatmoko
    - Japan and the Economic Development of Asia, October 29, 1973 (Folder 17)
    - Reflections on Non-Alignment in the 1970s, Djakarta, May 1973 (Folder 18)
    - The Role of the Medium and Small Nations in the New Asia-Pacific Setting, January 1973 (Folder 19)
    - SEA Regional Cooperation and Culture, October 1973 (Folder 20)
    - Soul and Society, address, Cedar Crest College, Allentown, PA, September 18, 1969 (Folder 21)
    - Statement at the Tokyo meeting of the Club of Rome, October 24-27, 1973 (Folder 22)
  - Soehandrio, Dr., speech, American Association, Djakarta, September 4, 1958 (Folder 23)
  - Soeharto, President, remarks, Vice President Agnew luncheon, May 26, 1970 (Folder 24)
  - Students' papers (Folder 25)
  - Students' papers (Box 57., Folder 1-4)
  - Subandrio
    - Speech on the occasion of UN Day, October 24, 1963 (Folder 5)
    - Statements at the United Nations, 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Subversive activities (Folder 7)
  - Sukarno, Achmed
    - General (Folder 8-9)
    - Address at International Solidarity Meeting of Students for the Liberation of West Irian, May 15, 1962 (Folder 10)
    - Address before the Heads of State or Government of Non-Aligned Countries, Beograd, September 1, 1961 (Folder 11)
    - Belgrade Conference speech, September 1, 1961 (Folder 12)
    - Clippings (Folder 13)
    - Clippings (Box 58., Folder 1)
    - Face the Nation appearance, January 31, 1965 (Folder 2)
    - Feith, Herbert, President Soekarno, the Army and the Communists: The Triangle Changes Shape, July 29, 1964 (Folder 3)
    - Feith, Herbert and J. Mackie, The Pressures On President Sukarno, article, Nation (Sydney), January 27, 1962 (Folder 4)
    - For Liberty and Justice, speech, Council For World Affairs, April 21, 1961 (Folder 5)
    - Jaquet-Francillon, Sukarno's War Against Malaysia, article, The New Republic, April 10, 1965 (Folder 6)
    - Jones, Garth N., Sukarno's Policy of Confrontation Against the Formation of the Malaysia Federation, n.d. (Folder 7)
    - Let Us Transform the World!, address at the Asian-African Journalists Conference, April 24, 1963 (Folder 8)
    - President's Conception, the, 1957 (Folder 9-12)
    - To Preserve the Republic We Have Proclaimed, speech, February 21, 1957 (Folder 13)
    - Tour to Kalimantan, West Irian, North Sulawesi, Solo, July-September 1957 (Folder 14)
    - Trip, May-June 1961 (Folder 15)
  - Sulawesi
    - General (Box 59., Folder 1)
    - Central Sulawesi (Folder 2)
    - National Conference, 1957 (Folder 3)
    - North Sulawesi
      - August 7, 1957 celebrations, speeches, etc. (Folder 4)
      - East Indonesian Youth Conference, July 1957 (Folder 5)
      - Financial and reconstruction matters (Folder 6)
      - History, 1957 (Folder 7)
      - Maengkom's Mission to, 1957 (Folder 8)
      - Permesta Movement (Folder 9)
      - Working Conference and Permesta Movement, 1957 (Folder 10)
    - South Sulawesi
      - General (Folder 11)
      - Security, 1954 (Folder 12)
      - The South Sulawesi Excavation Project, 1970 (Folder 13)
  - Sumatra
    - General (Folder 14)
    - General (Box 60., Folder 1)
    - Atjeh
      - 1955 (Folder 2)
      - Armed forces (Folder 3)
      - Autonomy and reconstruction, 1956-57 (Folder 4)
      - Barter system (Folder 5)
      - Report of Commission on Atjeh, February 17, 1954 (Folder 6)
      - Security (Folder 7)
    - Central Sumatra
      - General (Folder 8)
      - B.C. Movement (Folder 9)
      - Communist group (Folder 10)
      - Economic conditions (Folder 11)
      - General government policy, 1956-57 (Folder 12)
      - Murba (Folder 13)
      - Nationalist group (Folder 14)
      - Politics and government (Folder 15)
      - Regional and traditional groups (Folder 16)
      - Regional movement (Folder 17)
      - Religious groups (Folder 18)
    - Central and South Sumatra, security, 1954 (Folder 19)
    - North Sumatra
      - Clippings, 1957 (Box 61., Folder 1-2)
      - Government statement debates, 1953 (Folder 3)
      - Oilfields (Folder 4)
      - Security, 1954 (Folder 5)
    - South Sumatra
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Armed forces, 1957
        - General (Folder 7)
        - Military administration (Folder 8)
      - Dewan Garuda (Folder 9)
      - Economic conditions (Folder 10)
      - Groups
        - Demands and backgrounds, 1957 (Folder 11)
        - Against Daerah Movements, 1957 (Folder 12)
        - Left (Sarbupri, SOBSI, PKI) (Folder 13)
        - Regional (Folder 14)
      - Hatta (Folder 15)
      - MUSI dan SEKITARNJA (Folder 16)
      - PNI (Folder 17)
      - Political parties supporting Dewan Movements (Masjumi, PSII, N.U., Murba) (Folder 18)
      - Winarno's exit from, 1957 (Folder 19)
  - Surjotjondro, Sujono, address, American Indonesian Chamber of Commerce, New York City, January 12, 1956 (Box 62., Folder 1)